Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records and Drawings Collection PR 53
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- New York Produce Exchange - New York, NY
  - Proposed alterations: 22nd floor: typical tower plan; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1936-02-26 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): composite floor plan; blueprint on paper, 1931-10-07 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations: sketches of floor plans related to Bottomley, Wagner & White plan; graphite on trace, 2 sheets (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): 5th floor plan; photostat on paper, 1930-11-01 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): 3rd & 4th floor plan; photostat on paper, 1930-11-01 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): 2nd floor plan; photostat on paper, 1930-11-01 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): ground floor plan; photostat on paper, 1930-11-01 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): isometric; photostat on paper, 1930-11-01 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): 21st to 24th floor plan; photostat on paper, 1930-11-01 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): 17th-20th floor plan; photostat on paper, 1930-11-01 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): 13th-16th floor plan; photostat on paper, 1930-11-01 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): 11th & 12th floor plan; photostat on paper, 1930-11-01 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): 9th & 10th floor plan; photostat on paper, 1930-11-01 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): 7th & 8th floor plan; photostat on paper, 1930-11-01 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations (Bottomley, Wagner & White): 6th floor plan; photostat on paper, 1930-11-01 (Box 188-A)
  - Library story & library gallery plans; aniline on paper (Box 188-A)
  - Basement plan; aniline on paper (Box 188-A)
  - 1st office story plan; aniline on paper (Box 188-A)
  - 3rd office story plan; aniline on paper (Box 188-A)
  - 2nd office story plan; aniline on paper (Box 188-A)
  - 4th office story plan; aniline on paper (Box 188-A)
  - Safe Deposit Co. floor plan: memorandum of gas outlets; ink on linen, 190[?]-11-19 (Box 234)
  - Safe Deposit Co.: details of finish; ink on linen (Box 234)
  - Safe Deposit Co.: details of finish; ink on linen (Box 234)
  - Safe Deposit Co.: plan, elevation & section of vestibule; ink on linen (Box 234)
  - Plan of skylight over tanks & elevators at section 3; ink on linen (Box 234)
  - Safe Deposit Co.: plan & elevation of closets south of piers K & K1; ink on linen (Box 234)
  - Safe Deposit Co.: detail of doors & closets between M1 & L1; ink on linen (Box 234)
  - Safe Deposit Co.: plan & elevation of closets north of piers L & L1; ink on linen (Box 234)
  - Safe Deposit Co.: plan of boxes running east & west, south of piers K2 & K3; ink on linen (Box 234)
  - Safe Deposit Co.: elevation of windows; ink on linen (Box 234)
  - Safe Deposit Co.: plan of boxes in ladies room; ink on linen (Box 234)
  - Safe Deposit Co. [?]: unidentified plan; ink on linen (Box 234)
  - Lamppost; ink wash on paper, damaged (2 pieces) (Box 234)
  - Safe Deposit Co.: overhead work of hydraulic elevators with correspondence from Otis Bros.; blueprint on paper, ink on paper, 1883-04-09 (Box 234)
  - Arrangement of pipe work (Otis Bros.); blueprint on paper, 1883-08-13 (Box 234)
  - Piping plan for elevators with attached correspondence (Otis Bros.); blueprint on paper, 1883-10-05 (Box 234)
  - Detail of steam pump; blueprint on paper, 1882-04-18 (Box 234)
  - Worthington steam pump: plan showing location of nozzles & holding downbolts; blueprint on paper, damaged (2 pieces), 1879-02-11 (Box 234)
  - Arrangement of pipe work (Otis Bros.); blueprint on paper, 1883-12-31 (Box 234)
  - Arrangement of pipe work (Otis Bros.); blueprint on paper, 1883-08-03 (Box 234)
  - Structural: 1st story plan, sections 1-3; ink on linen, 4 sheets (Box 27)
  - Structural: main story plan, sections 1-3; ink on linen, 3 sheets (Box 27)
  - Structural: 6th tower story beam plan; ink on linen, 1883-05-02 (Box 27)
  - Iron work: 1st office story plan, sections 1-3; ink on linen, 3 sheets (Box 27)
  - Iron work: 2nd office story plan, sections 1-3; ink on linen, 3 sheets (Box 27)
  - Iron work: 3rd office story plan, sections 1-3; ink on linen, 3 sheets (Box 27)
  - Iron work: 4th office story plan, sections 1-3; ink on linen, 3 sheets (Box 27)
  - Iron work: roof tier plan, sections 1-3; ink on linen, 3 sheets (Box 27)
  - Iron work: details of column bases; ink on linen, 1882-03-18 (Box 27)
  - Elevator columns, basement; ink on linen (Box 27)
  - Structural: intermediate story plan; ink on linen, 1882-09-05 (Box 27)
  - Iron work: 1st story columns; ink on linen (Box 27)
  - Structural: library floor tier, section 3; ink on linen (Box 27)
  - Structural: library upper & lower galleries, section 3; ink on linen (Box 27)
  - Structural: 2nd tower story plan; ink on linen, 1883-04-17 (Box 27)
  - Structural: 5th tower story plan; ink on linen, 1883-04-24 (Box 27)
  - Structural: 4th tower story plan; ink on linen, 1883-04-21 (Box 27)
  - Structural: 3rd tower story plan; ink on linen, 1883-04-18 (Box 27)
  - East tower wall plan, cellar; ink on linen (Box 27)
  - 2nd office floor part plan; graphite on linen (Box 27)
  - Structural: tower - mezzanine story, section 1; ink on linen, 1882-02-21 (Box 27)
  - Structural: tower - intermediate story #2; ink on linen, 1882-02-21 (Box 27)
  - Structural: tower - intermediate story #3, section 1; ink on linen, 1882-02-21 (Box 27)
  - Structural: roof tier of tower; ink on linen (Box 27)
  - Structural: tower story #7; ink on linen, 1883-05-26 (Box 27)
  - Cellar & 1st story: iron work between piers M & N; ink on linen (Box 27)
  - Iron column details; ink on linen (Box 27)
  - Iron columns between 2nd & 3rd office stories; ink on linen (Box 27)
  - Iron columns for Safe Deposit Co.; ink on linen (Box 27)
  - Unidentified structural plan sketch; graphite & ink on trace, 1883-04-24 (Box 27)
  - Site plan; blueprint on paper (Box 27)
  - Transverse section on line A-B; ink & watercolor on paper & linen (damaged) (Box 229)
  - Interior finish: main room & library; ink & watercolor on paper & linen (Box 229)
  - Tower story plans; ink & watercolor on paper & linen (Box 229)
  - Library gallery plan; ink & watercolor on paper & linen (Box 229)
  - Interior finish: elevations of main room & halls; ink & watercolor on paper & linen (Box 229)
  - North elevation of tower; ink & watercolor on paper & linen (damaged) (Box 7-A)
  - Terra cotta for 3rd & 4th office stories, pier A; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta for 3rd & 4th office stories, south facade of tower; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - North facade of tower detail; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work in 1st story, piers 7, 8, 9 plans & elevations; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - South facade of tower detail; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta for 3rd & 4th office stories, pier oP; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Main story cornice, New Street: plans & elevation; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work in vault through tower; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - West facade of tower details; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Main story cornice, Stone St. plans & elevation; ink on linen (damaged) (Box 7)
  - Main story cornice, New St. plans & elevation; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Main story cornice, Broadway. plans & elevation; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work in 1st story, piers P7 & A7. plans & elevations; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work in 1st story, piers oP, P1, P2 & P5. plans & elevations; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Main story cornice, south elevation of tower. plans & elevation; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work, 1st & 2nd office stories; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Main story cornice, Beaver St. plans & elevation; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work, 1st & 2nd office stories; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work, 3rd & 4th office stories, pier A7; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work in 1st story, piers C7, A7, L7 & L8; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work, 1st & 2nd office stories. details; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - North facade of tower from main to 1st tower story floor; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work, 1st & 2nd office stories. detail; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work, 1st & 2nd office stories. detail; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work in 1st story, piers A, B, F & 1c; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Section of office stories; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work, 1st & 2nd office stories. detail; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work, 3rd & 4th office stories, pier L7; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta work, 3rd & 4th office stories, pier P7; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta caps, main story; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta caps, main story; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta filling for main cornice; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Round windows in tower; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - 1st story caps: Broadway, Stone, & Beaver Sts.; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - 1st story cornice: sections showing terra cotta junction with granite; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Terra cotta caps, main story; ink on linen (Box 7)
  - Layout of medallions; graphite on linen (2 sheets) (Box 7)
  - Detail of lettering; ink on linen (incomplete) (Box 7)
  - East facade of tower detail; aniline on paper (damaged, 2 pieces) (Box 7-A)
  - Granite work: piers oP & P1; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Granite work: piers P2, P5 & P7; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Plan & elevation of piers A5 & A4; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Plan & elevation of piers F & G; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Plan & elevation of piers A5 & A4; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Plan & elevation of piers P2 & P3; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Plan & elevation of piers P2 & P3; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Plan & elevation of piers F & G; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Granite work: piers A & B; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Granite work: piers A7, A6, A5, A2, A; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Granite work: piers L7, L8 & L9; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Granite work: piers P7, O7, L7, C7, A7; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Granite work: piers O7, O8, O9; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Granite work: piers F, I, N, oP; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Detail of driveway to the boiler room; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Arch between piers 12 & 13. isometric drawing of pier blocks; ink on linen, 1883-12-07 (Box 7-A)
  - Stairs: from passageway in tower to terrace, from passageway to 1st story; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Granite work in vault through tower; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Detail of base of porch, pier G; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Detail of base of porch, pier F; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Granite work in vault through tower; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Unidentified [pier] "A" detail, related to granite work; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Frieze for Broadway porches; ink on linen (Box 7-A)
  - Front elevation of terrace; ink on linen, 1883-12-11 (Box 7-A)
  - Detail of buttress & pier 12; ink on linen, 1883-12-06 (Box 7-A)
  - Detail of buttress & pier 13; ink on linen, 1883-12-08 (Box 7-A)
  - Piers 12 & 13: detail & elevations; ink on linen, 1883-12-07 (Box 7-A)
  - Arches from G to G2, L to L2, G5 to G7, etc., showing structural & decorative work; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Plan of offices, NW room; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Main room: elevation of main entrance, north end (Box 46)
  - Section of staircase from 1st story to intermediate story #1 looking north; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Call room & coat room details; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Doors & windows on line of library floor; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Main room: telephone boxes, settees & chairs; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Telegraph booths in main room; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Cross section through Beaver St. hall south of elevator shaft (looking south); ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Arch between piers N2 & N5; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Exterior doors & windows in area west of boiler room; ink on linen, 1884-01-23 (Box 46)
  - Detail of cornices & sash partitions, 1st story; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Finish of call room; ink on linen, 1884-01-17 (Box 46)
  - Section of vestibule north of staircase to intermediate story #1 looking north; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Interior elevation of main story - windows, south facade of tower; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Detail of wainscoting around piers, 1st story; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Cornices & sash partitions, 1st story; ink on linen (damaged) (Box 46)
  - Detail of cornice & sash partition between pier 04 & 03; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Section of vestibule & stair to intermediate story #1 looking south; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Arches from E5 to N5 & E2 to N2 showing structural & decorative work; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Plaster arches, piers p7 & OP main story; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Arches at south end of main room, pier P2 to P5; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Detail of cornices & sash partitions, 1st story btwn piers H7, H6, H5 & H4; ink on linen (damaged) (Box 46)
  - Piers, cornices & transoms from F to N & from F7 to O7; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Main story: detail of wainscoting around piers in main room (Box 46)
  - Elevation of 1st story hall looking west; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Detail of entrance doors in porches; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Section of vestibule north of staircase to intermediate story #1 looking south; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Water closets in cellar, Beaver St. end; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Detail of cornices & sash partitions, 1st story btwn piers I1 & I2; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Detail of elevator fronts in tower from cellar to 1st office story; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Skylight in main room; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Plan of hat & coat room; ink on linen, 1884-02-29 (Box 46)
  - Panel details for main room; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Section of wall & cornice [?]; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Unidentified section; ink on linen (damaged) (Box 46)
  - Main room: wash basins & changed wainscoting; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Soffit of transoms in main room; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Elevation of door btwn L7 & M7, 1st story; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Alteration of [rooms ?] 104 & 105; ink on linen, 1884-03-01 (Box 46)
  - Elevations for unidentified counter; ink on linen, 1983-11-14 (Box 46)
  - Flour inspection table; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Dress hook; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Elevations of main room doors; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Plan for alteration of rooms 125 & 126; ink on linen, 1884-02-12 (Box 46)
  - Detail of three doors of southeast corner of main room; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Section of [?] jamb, 1st story; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Alteration of elevator front in Beaver St. vestibule, 1st story; ink on linen, 1883-10-09 (Box 46)
  - Doors in office stories; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Office desks; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Flour tables; ink on linen (Box 46)
  - Windows in main room; ink on linen (damaged) (Box 46-A)
  - Lard & grain tables; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Telephone boxes; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Plan of vestibule & staircase, 1st story; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Alteration of rooms 352 & 354; ink on linen, 1884-02-19 (Box 46-A)
  - Door between pier A2 & B2, 1st story (Box 46-A)
  - Drawing of wainscot & sash partition, 1st story looking east; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Alteration of rooms 437 & 439; ink on linen, 1884-02-14 (Box 46-A)
  - Door to boiler room, elevation & section; ink on linen, 1884-01-16 (Box 46-A)
  - Alternate design for railing on telegraph booths in main room; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Alteration of tower story #5; ink on linen, 1884-02-25 (Box 46-A)
  - Engineer's office under terrace; ink on linen, 1884-02-20 (Box 46-A)
  - Plan of hat & coat room, main floor tower; ink on linen, 1884-03-01 (Box 46-A)
  - Finish of north & south end of elevators in Beaver St. halls; ink on linen, 1883-12-03 (Box 46-A)
  - Window trims for 1st & 2nd story, east & west fronts; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Plan of landing of tower story #1 & vestibule ceiling; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Section of tower vestibule & staircase looking west; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Elevation of rostrum in call room; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Detail of wainscoting, 1st story; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Main room, elevation of 4 door, north end; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Main room, detail of gallery; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Elevations of partitions; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Sections of stairs showing 1st & 2nd intermediate story landings; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Arches with ornamental panels, north end of main room, library floor level; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - East & west elevations of partition from A1 to E1 (Box 46-A)
  - Elevations of doors between B2 & C2 on main story & between A2 & E2 on library story; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Window trims, 3rd & 4th office story; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Section of stair between passageway & 1st story hall in tower; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Alteration of room 335; ink on linen, 1884-02-18 (Box 46-A)
  - Windows & sliding doors in rooms north of main room, main floor; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Plan & elevation of doors in hall on library floor; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Chairs for main room; graphite on trace (Box 46-A)
  - Alteration of room 303; ink on linen, 1884-02-13 (Box 46-A)
  - Rooms 211, 212: sash partition of private office, south elevation, 1884-01-04 (Box 46-A)
  - Alteration of 304 & 306; ink on linen, 1884-02-21 (Box 46-A)
  - Alteration of room in tower story #1; ink on linen (Box 46-A)
  - Alteration of rooms 337 & 339; ink on linen, 1884-02-13 (Box 46-A)
  - Alteration of rooms 111 & 112; ink on linen, 1984-03-03 (Box 46-A)
  - Alteration of rooms 211 & 212; ink on linen, 1884-01-04 (Box 46-A)
  - Alteration of rooms 119, 120 & 121; ink on linen, 1884-02-13 (Box 46-A)
  - Alteration of rooms 113 & 114; ink on linen, 1884-02-14 (Box 46-A)
  - Heat & vent: elevation of wall on Broadway & Whitehall St. showing flues, etc.; aniline on paper, 2 sheets (Box 46-A)
  - Beams for 4th office story water closets; aniline on paper (Box 46-A)
  - Elevator cars; aniline on paper (damaged) (Box 188-A)
  - Telephone boxes in main room; aniline on paper (Box 188-A)
  - Interior column & panel detail; aniline on paper (Box 188-A)
  - Plan of Beaver St. skylight; aniline on paper (Box 188-A)
  - Sash partition, 1st office story; aniline on paper (Box 188-A)
  - Hydraulic passenger elevators; blueprint on paper, 1883-05-10 (Box 188-A)
  - Overhead work of passenger elevator; blueprint on paper (2 pieces), 1883-03-19 (Box 188-A)
  - Hall elevation of arch entrance to main room, line of main floor; ink on paper (Box 188-A)
  - Partition from A1 to E1 looking west, NW room main floor; ink on paper (Box 188-A)
  - Plan of foundtions showing piling, sections 1-3; ink on linen (3 sheets) (Box 42)
  - Plan of foundtions showing piers, sections 1 & 3; ink on linen (2 sheets) (Box 42)
  - Elevation of caps and bond stones in pier 18, basement; ink on linen (Box 42)
  - Plan of stone caps under elevator columns, section 3; ink on linen (Box 42)
  - Section through north end of court; ink on linen (Box 42)
  - Plan of stone caps and boiler vault, sections 1 & 2; ink on linen (Box 42)
  - Drawings of piers; ink on paper, 4 sheets (brittle) (Box 42)
  - Elevation of granite work to be pieced out Pier L9, 1st story; ink on paper, 1884-01-26 (Box 42)
  - Elevations of foundation; ink on paper (brittle, damaged) (Box 42)
  - Plan of weights on foundation on line; ink on paper (brittle, damaged) (Box 42)
  - Pier L8, M7 & N7; ink on linen (Box 42)
  - Engineering survey; blueprint on paper, 1930-09-19 (Box 42)
  - Unidentified measurements & notes; graphite on paper, 3 sheets (Box 42)
  - Lot plan (recto), diagrammatic sketch (verso); ink/graphite on paper, 1936-01 (Box 42)
  - Library story piers: bond stones, elevations; ink on paper (Box 37)
  - Sections of piers M7, N7, L7 in office stories; ink on paper (Box 37)
  - Sections of piers M7, N7, L7 in main and mezzanine floors; ink on paper, ink on linen flap (Box 37)
  - Piers B2, C2 & D2 through main and library floors; ink on paper (Box 37)
  - Plans and elevations of L7; ink on paper (Box 37)
  - Piers B2, C2 & D2 main story elevations; ink on paper (brittle) (Box 37)
  - Plan & elevation of E3, 1st floor; ink on paper, ink on linen flap (Box 37)
  - Plan & elevation of C2 & D2, 1st floor; ink on paper (Box 37)
  - Drawing of porches on Broadway, Whitehall, Beaver & Stone St., elevations & plans of piers; ink on paper (Box 37)
  - Drawing of piers E3, E4, D4, C4, B4, B5; ink on paper (Box 37)
  - Drawings of pier L7; ink on paper (Box 37)
  - Detail of arch between piers N2 & N5; ink on paper (brittle, damaged) (Box 37)
  - Lower line of arch, main room; ink on paper (brittle) (Box 37)
  - Lower line of arch, main room; ink on paper (brittle) (Box 37)
  - Detail of arch from pier N5 to P5; ink on paper (brittle) (Box 37)
  - Beaver St. stoop steps between A piers; ink on paper (brittle, damaged) (Box 37)
  - Brick details for 3rd office story; ink on paper (brittle, damaged) (Box 37)
  - Stone St. stoops between P piers; ink on paper (brittle, damaged) (Box 37)
  - First story: plaster caps, cornices & transoms; ink & watercolor on linen (Box 273-A)
  - Plan of terrace; ink on linen, 1883-10-19 (Box 273-A)
  - Street railing; ink on linen (Box 273-A)
  - Door in 1st story btwn A2 & B2; ink on linen (Box 273-A)
  - Memorandum drawing of terrace beams; graphite & ink on linen (Box 273-A)
  - Piers M7 & N7, 1st floor; ink on linen (Box 273-A)
  - Details of 1st story column bases; ink on linen (Box 273-A)
  - Plan of terrace showing joints of blue stone flags; graphite on trace, 1884-01-29 (Box 273-A)
  - Exterior stair on Stone St.; ink on linen, 1883-10-31 (Box 273-A)
  - Detail of floor arches; ink on linen (Box 273-A)
  - Detail of lintels over 3rd office story windows; ink on linen (Box 273-A)
  - Unidentified stair; ink on linen (Box 273-A)
  - Plan showing pitch of roofs; ink on linen (Box 273-A)
  - Library floor: section of partition from A5 to D5; ink on linen (Box 273-A)
  - Blue stone sills; ink on linen (Box 273-A)
  - Memorandum for corner stone box; graphite on paper, 2 sheets (Box 273-A)
  - Iron work btwn piers C7 & A7, cellar & 1st story; aniline on paper (Box 46-A)
  - Main story plan showing transoms; aniline on paper (Box 46-A)
  - First story plan showing transoms; aniline on linen (Box 46-A)
  - North end of west wall of court, office stories; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box 273-A)
  - Plan of skylight walls; blueprint on paper (damaged, 2 pieces) (Box 273-A)
  - [?] columns, basement; blueprint on paper (damaged, fragment) (Box 273-A)
  - Tower: section through archway; blueprint on paper (damaged, 2 pieces) (Box 273-A)
  - Iron work: columns G1, h1, etc., mezz to 1st office sty; aniline on paper (brittle) (Box 401)
  - Iron work: columns a1, b1, etc., library to 1st office sty; aniline on paper (brittle) (Box 401)
  - Iron work: tower elevation columns; aniline on paper (brittle) (Box 401)
  - Iron work: columns a, b, etc., library to 1st office sty; aniline on paper (brittle) (Box 401)
  - Iron work: columns a1, b1, etc., 3rd to 4th office sty; aniline on paper (brittle) (Box 401)
  - Iron work: columns a, b, etc., 1st to 2nd office sty; aniline on paper (brittle) (Box 401)
  - Iron work: columns a, b, etc., 2nd to 3rd office sty; aniline on paper (brittle) (Box 401)
  - Iron work: columns a1, b1, etc., 2nd to 3rd office sty; aniline on paper (brittle) (Box 401)
  - Iron work: columns a1, b1, etc., 1st to 2nd office sty; aniline on paper (brittle) (Box 401)